ezybonds.com 2018-01-15

# Ezybonds Global Payments

Privacy Policy

Data Protection  
Any information you provide us with will only be disclosed in accordance with laws of your legal jurisdiction.

Required Information  
To open an Ezyaccount you must tell us your name, email address, date of birth and postal address. For security, you must also submit your password and may be required to answer a security question. In order to deposit money into your Ezyaccount and make withdrawals you need to register your debit card or bank account details. We only collect the information that is required for us to process your transactions securely and protect you against fraud.

Transaction Information  
In order to process a transaction, we need to know the amount of money sent or requested and the email address of the parties involved.

Disclosure of Information  
We will NEVER disclose any of your personal information without your consent. Your debit card, bank account details or Ezyaccount account balance will NEVER be revealed to anyone you have paid or who has paid you. This makes Ezyaccount transactions more private and secure than sending a Cheque or using your debit card.

Aggregate Statistical Information  
We may collect aggregated statistical information for purposes of improving our service and your experience with Ezyaccount. This data does not contain personally identifying information, such as your name or email address.

Cookies  
We use a cookie to display your email address, so that you don't have to retype it each time you log in to your account. No personal information is held within this cookie.

Emails  
As an Ezyaccount member You agree to accept any emails from us at any time.

Changing Information  
You can update your account information in the personal details section of the Ezyaccount web site.

Further Questions  
If you have any questions about your privacy or this privacy statement, please email us at [support@ezybonds.com](mailto:support@ezybonds.com)
